Finding aid to the Graduate Work records CA.MS.01011
Smith College Archives
Graduate Work records
1919-2018
Smith College Archives
Smith College. School for Social Work.
CA.MS.01011
11.458 linear feet (34 containers)
Graduate Work records include files on individuals who did graduate work at Smith and information on Smith graduate programs and non-degree programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials in the Smith College Archives are open for use, with the following exceptions: "Office Files," files of records created for the use of the administrative unit that created them, are closed to research for a period of 10 years following their creation. Student academic records, student disciplinary records, and all records containing FERPA-covered student information are closed during the lifetime of the student. Student records created 100 years or more ago are assumed to be about deceased students. In all cases, the College Archives will continue to provide public access to materials that were intended to be public at the time of their creation (press releases, publications, etc.)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown.
Other Finding Aids
Many parts of the collection have container lists that are available upon request by contacting specialcollections@smith.edu
Scope and Contents
Graduate Work records include files on individuals who did graduate work at Smith; information on Smith graduate programs (such as the Summer Schools of Italian and Music, the masters program in Physical Education, and the School for Social Work); and non-degree programs (such as the Institute for the Coordination of Women's Interests, Alumnae College, and the Project on Women and Social Change). Additional program records are filed elsewhere.
Related Materials
Office of Graduate Studies
Related Materials
Se also Smith College School for Social Work records.
Smith College. School for Social Work.; Smith College. Department of Graduate Studies.; Alumnae College; Smith College. Department of Graduate Studies.; Alumnae College; Smith College. School for Social Work.
- General A-Pamphlets (Box 1281)
- General ph-z including Grad Students Association minutes and presidents book (Box 1282)
- Individuals a-d (Box 1283)
- Individuals e-l (Box 1284)
- Individuals m-ri (Box 1285)
- Individuals ro-z (Box 1286)
- Individuals: Berkman, Tessie Dora MSS, 1933 (Box 1287)
- Individuals: Mary Ruth Carson thesis (Box 1288)
- Individuals: Gretchen de Schot: course notes, lesson plans (Box 1289)
- Individuals: Kirsty P. MacCalman thesis (Box 1290)
- Individuals: Julia MacKenzie DIPL, 1979 (Box 1290.1)
- Individuals: Patience Wheeler Norman AB and AM, 1935, 1943 (Box 1291)
- Individuals: Marulyn Raab MSW, 1955 (Box 1291.1)
- Individuals; Joiy Brickner Rabinowitz general and course notes (Box 1292)
- Individuals M-Ri (Box 1293)
- Center for the Study of Social and Political Change (Box 1302)
- Summer School of Italian;Summer School of Music (Box 1305)
- Graduate course: Teachers of Physical Education (Box 1306)
- Physical Education graduate student permanent record cards (Box 1306.1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  CLOSED
- Alumni newsletter, 1944; 1949-74 (Box 1307)
- Alumnae Association National Executive Committee correspondence (Box 1310.1)
- Alumnae Association National Executive Committee minutes, alumnae publications (Box 1311)
- B - case studies (Box 1312)
- Curriculum cont'd - F (Box 1313)
- Smith College Studies in So cial Work, Volumes 24, 25, 34-36, 1953-1966 (Box 1313.1)
- School for Social Work luncheon notices: G (Box 1314)
- School for Social Work luncheon notices Z, 1999 (Box 1314.1)
- School for Social Work student organization photo albums, 2000-2002 (Box 1314.2)
- School for Social Work photographs (Box 1315)
- School for Social work publications (Box 1316)
- School for Social Work publications (Box 1317)
- School for Social Work publications: journals and catalogues (Box 1318)
- School for Social Work publication: In Depth (Box 1318.1)
- Smith Management Program (Box 1319)
- Photographs of School for Social Work classes, 1947-2004; Accession 2018-A-0020; 0.04 linear feet (2 regular folders and 1 envelope in a box with multiple other accessions; 1 oversize flat folder )
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transfer from the School for Social Work, Alumnae Relations and Development Office
  - School for Social Work class photos, 1947-2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box CA Shared 1)
  - School for Social Work reunion photos, 1968, 1970, 1985, 2008; 1 folders (1 envelope) (Box CA Shared 1)
  - School for Social Work miscellaneous photos, 1950, 1958, 1960, 1988, 1990; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box CA Shared 1)
  - Classes of 2003 and 2004 photos, 2003, 2004 (Folder OV)